# **Devin Williams**

Moreno Valley, CA hiredevin@gmail.com - 909-368-8037

CAREER OBJECTIVE: To obtain a challenging position, with an innovative and ambitious company with room to grow in a challenging work environment.

## HIGHLIGHTS OF QUALIFICATIONS:

Over nine years professional experience acquired in the administrative/customer service industry

Ability to work independently and as a part of a team

Ability to diffuse difficult situations and resolve conflict

Ability to manage a multitude of project at the same time; reliable and prompt, time management skills

Maintain professional and courteous manner with high volume Inbound/outbound calls

Computer knowledgeable, general office duties: typing, data entry, operating office machines, and sorting mail

#### **EDUCATION:**

San Joaquin Valley College - Rancho Cucamonga, CA

12/2015 - Expected Graduation Date - Associate of Science Degree in Administrative Health Care Management

COURSES/SKILLS:EHR, ICD-9-CM/ICD-10-CM Coding, First Aid/CPR Certified, CPT and HCPCS Coding, Typing 45 WPM, Medical Insurance Principles, Medical Terminology, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft PowerPoint, Outlook, & Microsoft Word

### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY:

03/2013 - PRESENT - Customer Order Management Representative II, Cardinal Health, Ontario, CA Answer incoming phone calls from customers, caregivers, and applicable referral sources. Process customer orders, ask appropriate information for billing purposes and follow up as necessary. Respond to customer questions and problems. Follow up on refused orders and orders that are returned without notification with customers and referrals .Process returns or exchange of product. Contact customers to inform them of additional information or payment needed.

05/2010-05/2011 - Customer Service Rep, Time Warner Cable, Ontario, CA

Provided information and assistance on all aspects of cables services, including sales to potential and current customers. Provided information regarding products and services, billing, repair, collections and responded to other types of inquiries.

03/2006-08/2009 - Customer Service Manager/Loan Support Specialist, Hartman Mortgage, City of Industry, CA

Monitored 25 employees with high volume inbound/outbound calls advising prospects, regarding their mortgage, collected and analyzed customers' information and documentation regarding income, assets, and credit information. Helped accurately create and maintain loan/mortgage applications.

11/2007-04/2008 - American Express Client Management, US Payment Solutions, Ontario, CA (part time) Provided customer service to American Express merchants with an annual review of their business's financial performance, also informed merchants about rate increases and handled objections to new rate and merchants questions and concerns.

06/2006-03/2007 - Leasing Consultant, APT Personnel Staffing, Colton, CA (on-call)

Greeting visitors and answering multi-phone line, tour prospective residents, prepared lease documentation, and completing move-in procedures also verified employment and rental history as well as credit checks.

03/2004-08/2006 – Customer Service/Telemarketer, Hartman Mortgage, City of Industry, CA Dealt with high volume inbound/outbound calls advising prospects, regarding their mortgage options for refinance, Help determine which financial products best meet the prospects needs and financial circumstances.

07/1999-12/2003 - Customer Service/ Billing Sales, Daily Bulletin, Ontario, CA Answer high volume inbound calls, respond to orders, general customer inquiries, invoice questions, and customer complaints, also dealt with billing/collections and credit card transaction over the phone.

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

I'm a reliable professional who consistently demonstrates integrity and sound judgment. I perform all tasks with enthusiasm and efficiency. Well organized and manage my time and assignments wisely, while using accuracy as my basis for completing my task. I work very well with others in a team atmosphere and I'm just as effective while working independently. I possess great customer skills, which has allowed me to establish excellent rapport with the general public while demonstrating the skills to actively listen to others. Excellent problem solving abilities, while understanding the importance of following up on all matters in order to obtain the desired resolution.